<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Evillgenius75: An Enterprise Application Architect in the Cloud on Evillgenius75 Gitpage</title>
    <link>https://evillgenius75.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Evillgenius75: An Enterprise Application Architect in the Cloud on Evillgenius75 Gitpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 16:24:11 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://evillgenius75.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Suggested Readings, Links, Podcasts and other Sundry Items for the Burgeoning Cloud Architect</title>
      <link>https://evillgenius75.github.io/posts/04252022-archibooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 16:24:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evillgenius75.github.io/posts/04252022-archibooks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here I present a list of resources I have used or am currently using to further my knowldege in the Application Architecture space with a purposeful focus on Cloud Native development and Distributed Systems design. I would love to hear of other resources, you my reader, may have found useful in your journey in Modern Application design.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://evillgenius75.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evillgenius75.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Your Humble Author   I am Eddie Villalba! Professionally I am an Enterprise Application Modernization Architect for Google Cloud. My responsibilities include consulting with Google’s most strategic customers in North America on Cloud Native Microservice and DevOps using Container Orchestration technologies and following Cloud Native Computing patterns and practices.
Previously, I held senior technical roles over an 11 year tenure at Microsoft. My experience in Enterprise Architecture Design, Distributed Systems Design and Data Center modernization have allowed me to work with many of the Forbes 100 Companies and US Federal Government Agencies developing strategic Software Delivery and Life Cycle plans and implementations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
